

PERSONAL INFORMATION



PRESENT ADDRESS MIRPUR-1, DHAKA, BANGLADESH (1216) PERMANENT ADDRESS BOALIA,1, GOBINDAGANJ, GAIBANDHA(5740)

FATHER'S NAME- ABU FATTAB SHAH MD. ELEAS **MOTHER'S NAME- MST. SAHANA BEGUM**

GENDER- MALE

HEIGHT-173.7cm WEIGHT- 55kg

MARITAL STATUS- SINGLE

DATE OF BIRTH- 1998-06-10

NATIONALITY- BANGLADESHI NID NO- 19983223004000007

PASSPORT NO- EA0382618

EMAIL ACCOUNT



radwanromy@gmail.com

radwanromy@outlook.com



CONTACT NUMBER

+8801717799111 (Bangladeshi Calls)

Brother's Phone No: +8801773589616 (Emergency Calls)



accwebdev.ezyro.com/portfolio https://github.com/radwanromy

ONLINE PROFILE

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~013f8d996be1d5fdd3 **GITHUB**

https://github.com/radwanromy

https://www.linkedin.com/in/a-s-m-radwan-316597155

HACKER RANK

https://www.hackerrank.com/radwanromy

LEETCODE

https://leetcode.com/radwanromy/

TIMUS ONLINE JUDGE

https://acm.timus.ru/A.S.M, Radwan

RESEARCHGATE

https://www.researchgate.net/profile/A_S_M_Radwan

FACEBOOK

https://www.facebook.com/radwan.romy.100

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

- JAVA
- Python C
- C+
- C#
- LUA

Software Quality Testing

- Selenium
- Web load
- Agileload
- W3C CSS validator

Operating Systems

- Windows 10,8,7,XP
- Android
- IOS

Developing Tools

- **PvCharm**
- Intrllij IDEA

A. S. M. RADWAN

To obtain full-time remote job in which I can contribute my years of software engineer professional experience, 4 years of engineering education and 8 years of work experience with computer works, as well as my collaboration and communication skills.

CARRER & APPLICATION INFORMATION

- Looking For: Mid-Level Remote Job
- Preferred Job Category: Software Engineer / Full-Stack Developer /Android Developer /Website Developer / Front-End Developer
- Available For: Part Time / Full Time
- Preferred District: Dhaka

WORK EXPERIENCE



MARCH 2021 - CONTINUING

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & JAPANESE LANGUAGE AND BUSINESS CULTURE TRAINEE

- B-JET (BANGLADESH-JAPAN ICT ENGINEERS' TRAINING PROGRAM)
 - WEBSITE LINK : https://bjet.org/

JANUARY 2022 - FEBRUARY 2022



SOFTWARE ENGINEER TRAINEE • ERA-INFOTECH LIMITED

- WORK TYPE: FULL-STACK DEVELOPER
- WEBSITE LINK: https://www.erainfotechbd.com/
- BACJK-END : SPRING BOOT WITH JAVA 13
- FRONT-END: ANGULAR 13 WITH CUSTOM CSS DESIGN
- I have worked on 3 big projects till now:
- 1. Bank Asia Credit Card Fund Transfer System (Python Django, Oracle).
- 2. Bank Locker Service (Spring Boot, Angular-13, Hibernate, Oracle).
- 3. ERA Blog App (Spring Boot, Angular-13, Hibernate, MySQL).

Currently Working on: E-Payment App(Spring Boot, Angular-13, Hibernate, Oracle)

OCTOBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021



SOFTWARE ENGINEER TRAINEE(INTERN) • ERA-INFOTECH LIMITED

- WORK TYPE: FULL-STACK DEVELOPER
- WEBSITE LINK: https://www.erainfotechbd.com/

MAY 2021-SEPTEMBER 2021



TEACHING ASSISTANT • COMPUTER GRAPHICS • AIUB

WORK TYPE: TEACHING

MAY 2020-JUNE 2020

WEBSITE LINK : https://cs.aiub.edu/

DECEMBER 2020-JANUARY 2020



WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT • DEVELOPER • UP-WORK

- WORK TYPE: GAME STREAMING
- WEBSITE LINK: https://www.sizzle.gg/

WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT • DEVELOPER • CRYSTAL COMMUNITY CENTER

- EVENT TYPE : COMMUNITY HALL
- WEBSITE LINK: http://crystalcc.unaux.com/

MAY 2018- SEPTEMBER 2021

- RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT TEAM AIUB COMPUTER CLUB TYPE: GENERAL MEMBER
- WEBSITE LINK : http://crystalcc.unaux.com/
- Contribute on building those websites : AIUB CYBER GAMIN FEST 2019 http://cgf.aiubcc.org/
- EVENT NAME : JARVIS 2.0 INTRA ACC CARNIVAL & WEBSITE LINK : http://jarvis.aiubcc.org/

EDUCATION

AMERICAN INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY BANGLADESH (AIUB), DHAKA



- PROGRAM: BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING
- STUDENT ID:18-36384-1 CGPA:3.70 CREDIT(S) COMPLETED: 148

GOVT. A. H. COLLEGE, BOGURA (GOVT. AHC, BOGURA) (2015-2017)



• EXAM PASSED: HSC (HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE)

• FROM SCIENCE GROUP WITH GPA 4.75

GOVT. GOBINDAGANJ BAHUMUKHI HIGH SCHOOL (2011-20 14)



- EXAM PASSED: SSC (SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE)
- FROM SCIENCE GROUP WITH GPA 5.00 (GOLDEN)

EXTRA EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

CISCO NETWORKING ACADEMY

- IT ESSENTIAL [CERTIFIED]
- CYBER SECUIRTY [CERTIFIED]



- **GOLand**
- Eclipse IDE
- AndroidStudio
- Netbeans
- Wordpress
- Blender
- VS Code

Designing Tools

- AutoCAD
- Adobe
- Krita
- Unity 3D

Database Tools

- XAMPE
- MySQL
- Oracle PLSOL



LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

- EXCELLENT Speaking in English, Bangla & Hindi.
- **EXCELLENT Writing & Reading in English & Bangla**

SPECIALIZATION & PROJECTS

- 1. Library Management Software (JAVA & SQL) Banknotes Authentication Classification (Python & Jupiter :: Anaconda)
- 2. Sheba Publications (Database Project, Oracle ,MySQL)
- 3. University Online Course Registration System (Software Quality Assurance and Testing)
- 4. Educational Portal Modification (EPM) (software Engineering project)
- 5. Poultry And Frozen Food Company Management Software



- 6. Ultimate Travel Package (Object Oriented Analysis & Design)
- 7. ERP based: A poultry and frozen food company software (Software Engineering)
- 8. Vacuum Cleaner Agent (Artificial-Intelligence)
- 9. Ultimate Travel Management System (OOP2 C#)
- 10. Basic Virtual Assistant (Python)
- 11. Scientific and Basic Both Calculator (C#)
- 12. Village View (Computer Graphics)
- 13. Hotel Management System (C-Sharp)
- 14. Game Streaming Website (Full Stack)
- 15. Django Web Frame Work (Python)

AREAS OF EXPERTISE (SKILLS)

- 2. **JAVA**
- PHP 3.
- 4. **REACT.JS**
- **RUBY ON RAILS** 5.
- 6. OOP
- DATA
- STRUCTURE
- 8. **ALGORITHMS**
- LARAVEL 9
- 10. **WORDPRESS**
- **JAVASCRIPT**
- HTML 12
- 13. CSS
- 14. JQUERY
- 15. MYSQL
- 16. GAMING
- 17. DRAWING
- 18. C#

- 19. SPRING BOOT
- 20. DJANGO
- 21. LUA 22. LOVE 2D
- 23. PLSQL
- 24. TOAD
- 25. HIBERNATE
- 26. ANGULAR 13
- 27. AWS
- 28. SAP
- 29. ERP
- GIT 30.
- 31. ATOM
- 32. BRACKETS
- 33. VS STUDIO 34. VS CODE
- 35. LATEX
- 36. MS OFFICE
- 37. CMD HANDLE

Signature



- INTERNET OF THINGS [CERTIFIED]
- INTRODUCTION TO PACKET TRACER [CERTIFIED]
- OPERATING SYSTEM [CERTIFIED]

LINKEDIN PREMIUM

- BECOME A FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER
- PHP ESSENTIAL TRAINING
- REACT.JS ESSENTIAL TRAINING
- RUBY ON RAILS 5 ESSENTIAL TRAINING

COURSERA.ORG, UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN COLLEGE OF LITERATURE, SCIENCE, AND THE ARTS

- PYTHON 3 (PYTHON FOR EVERYBODY)[CERTIFIED]
- **AWS S3 Basics by Coursera Project Network**

COURSERA.ORG, UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA SAN DIEGO & NATIONAL RESEARCH UNIVERSITY HIG HER SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS

ALGORITHMIC TOOLBOX [CERTIFIED]

COURSERA.ORG,GOOGLE AR & VR

INTRODUCTION TO AUGMENTED REALITY AND ARCORE

UDFMY

- SEO TUTORIAL [CERTIFIED]
- ADVANCED DATA STRUCTURES [CERTIFIED]
- INTRODUCTION TO PAYTHON PROGRAMMING [CERTIFIED]

SOLOLEARN

- HTLM 5 [CERTIFIED]
- PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE C++ [CERTIFIED]

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR



Exploit 2019 [FORMER] MindSparks-20 2020 [FORMER]

Bangladesh Innovation Forum [ACTIVE]

National Engineering Contest 2019 [FORMER]

MIST Robotics Club - Robolution-2019 [FORMER] BUP Robotics Club and BUP InfoTech Club [FORMER]

VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE

International Conference On Robotics And Signal Processing Techniques 2019 (ICREST 2019)

1st National Conference On Brian Engineering

AIUB Cyber Gaming Fest 2019

AIUB CS FEST 2018

Samsung eSports championship 2019

Youth Festival 2018 by Bangladesh ICT Division (Representative)

Cyber Security Challenge by Basis at AIUB

PARTICIPATION

- AIUB (ICREST 2019)
- **BUET CSE FEST 2019**
- **BUET EEE DAY 19** VIRTUAL REALITY FESTIVAL 2018 AT AIUB (RANK 4)
- DEVELOPERS WORKSHOP" BY BDAPPS.COM
- MINDSPARKS 2019 AT AUST
- ADVANCE GRAPHIC DESIGN BY ACC
- BUP ICT FEST AT BUP
- AIUB CS FEST 2018
- CYBER SECURITY CHALLENGE BY BASIS AT AIUB GOOGLE DEVELOPERS FESTIVAL 2018 BY GOOGLE
- INTERACTIVE AND PRACTICAL TRAINING SESSION WITH VIRTUAL REALITY BY ESAB AT AIUB
- ANDROID DEVELOPMENT WORKSHOP AT AIUB BANANI CAMPUS
- YOUTH FESTIVAL 2018 BY BANGLADESH ICT DEVESION AT HATIRJHIL
- ACC PROTAL DEVELOPMENT WORKSHOP BY ACC AT AIUB
- AORUS WORKSHOP BY GIGABYTE SUZUKI HAYABUSA WORKSHOP BY SUZUKI
- NATIONAL ENGINEERING CONTEST 2019 TECHFERNO

AWARDS AND HONORS

THE DUKE OF EDINBURGH'S INTERNATIONAL AWARD

GOLD BADGE ACHIEVER. (2021)

DURATION 18 MONTHS. NOVEMBER 2019 – JUNE 2021

National Mobile Application Development -

Bangladesh ICT Division (2020) [Passed]

BD Skills [Programming Assessment] Certification -Bangladesh Computer Council (2020)

শতবর্ষ জয়ন্তী ২০১১ – Rank 1st (2011) উৎসবে গণিত অলিম্পিয়াড (2011)

জাতীয় বিপ্লব মেধাবী পুরস্কার ২০০৭–

Rank 3rd (2007)























